<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>BLOG_NAME</title>
 <link href="YOUR_URL/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="YOUR_URL"/>
 <updated>2013-10-16T16:36:54-07:00</updated>
 <id>BLOG_URL</id>
 <author>
   <name>BLOG_NAME</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>California descriptions and navigating the supplier index</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/california-descriptions-and-navigating-the-supplier-index.html"/>
   <updated>2013-10-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/california-descriptions-and-navigating-the-supplier-index</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve been working closely with our Californian suppliers to create the best matching experience for custom manufacturing, and to show some love we&#39;ve added basic company descriptions for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/guides/unitedstates/california/3dprinting&quot;&gt;all 3D printing suppliers based in the Golden State&lt;/a&gt;. People from all over the world submit RFQs through SupplyBetter, and supplier descriptions are just one way to help find the right match for their projects. Since our last update we&#39;ve worked with suppliers to add equipment data, as well as reviews. To help buyers navigate our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/suppliers&quot;&gt;supplier index&lt;/a&gt; we&#39;ve added a key to quickly illustrate which kinds of information are available for each supplier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog/images/supplier_index_key.png&quot; alt=&quot;Supplier index legend&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our goal remains the same: to create the best marketplace for buyers to find suppliers. A marketplace that is convenient for buyers, fair for suppliers, and is the first place to go when it&#39;s time to make your custom mechanical parts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re always listening for feedback, so feel free to let us know what you think at feedback@supplybetter.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rob&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Suppliers can now claim and edit their company profiles</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/suppliers-can-now-claim-and-edit-their-company-profiles.html"/>
   <updated>2013-08-30T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/suppliers-can-now-claim-and-edit-their-company-profiles</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The SupplyBetter team is constantly working to maintain the most comprehensive database of 3D printing suppliers, and we are pleased to announce that suppliers can now claim and edit their own profiles in our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/suppliers&quot;&gt;Supplier Index&lt;/a&gt;. By uploading custom company descriptions, details about their machines, and company photos suppliers can use this support material to really make their profile stand on its own. Doing so allows our customers to better understand each company and improves the intelligence of how SupplyBetter matches. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/orders/new&quot;&gt;Submit an RFQ&lt;/a&gt; today and discover the best suppliers to make your custom parts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply meshing about,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rob&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Announcing the Launch of Supplier Profiles</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/announcing-the-launch-of-supplier-profiles.html"/>
   <updated>2013-07-15T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/announcing-the-launch-of-supplier-profiles</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re excited to announce that we’re launching &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/suppliers&quot;&gt;supplier profiles&lt;/a&gt; for 3D Printing.&lt;/strong&gt; We’ve been hard at work these past few months helping people get their custom mechanical parts made and this is just one more way we hope to make the experience better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s how this works:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Browse through our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/suppliers&quot;&gt;supplier profiles&lt;/a&gt; to see if there is a supplier that matches your spec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/orders/new&quot;&gt;“Get a Quote”&lt;/a&gt; to upload your part and submit a Request for Quote (RFQ)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit back and let the magic happen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Our passion is to be the best source for getting your parts made, and we do this by presenting the suppliers we believe are best able to fulfill your needs. Our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/orders/new&quot;&gt;standard RFQ&lt;/a&gt; has already helped our customers achieve this, and we hope Supplier Profiles will make shopping for service bureaus even faster and more informative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rob&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Tips to Improve Your RFQs</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/tips-to-improve-your-requests-for-quotes.html"/>
   <updated>2013-07-02T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/tips-to-improve-your-requests-for-quotes</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Filling out a proper &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/orders/new&quot;&gt;Request for Quote (RFQ)&lt;/a&gt; is the often the first contact a potential customer has with a supplier. To give our users the greatest chance at success, here’s our advice for how to get the most out of our RFQ service here at SupplyBetter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Files&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;STLs are the most common file type for 3D printing and have the widest acceptance, but we’re willing accept any file type as long as it’s relevant to your project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quantity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Must be a number. If your requirement is more along the lines of “100 a month” or “50,000 pieces annually with quarterly POs”, then write those details in the “Final Notes” section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drawing Units&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mars_Climate_Orbiter&quot;&gt;Satellites crash&lt;/a&gt; if the units are wrong, so best double check this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve dealt with everything from production-level parts to beginner sculptures, so feel free to reach out to us if you want help picking your material. Also, check our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.supplybetter.com/materials&quot;&gt;Materials page&lt;/a&gt; if you’re looking for other resources on how to decide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Postal Code and Country&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The minimum necessary for us to produce a quote that factors in shipping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Particular Suppliers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is anyone in particular you’d like SupplyBetter to compare against, just enter their name here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Message to Suppliers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is arguably the most important section of the RFQ. Suppliers love to get as much of an idea of just what it is you’re working on so they can understand your application and provide the best quote possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy requesting,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rob&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Blog</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/the-blog.html"/>
   <updated>2013-06-12T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/the-blog</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here at SupplyBetter, we aim to give buyers the best way to decide among suppliers, and to help suppliers by offering them the opportunity to quote the type of work that fits them best. We&#39;re starting off in 3D printing, and expanding to other manufacturing processes once we&#39;re ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we&#39;ll explore interesting technical and mechanical challenges, feature suppliers that do a great job for their buyers, and explain new features as SupplyBetter continues to improve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matt&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>